# MARIIA OMETSINSKA

# EDITOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

mariiaometsinska.github.io mariiaometsinska@gmail.com +48 791 352 649 Wroclaw, Poland

Diligent graphic designer with extensive experience in utilizing Adobe Creative Suite, DaVinci Resolve, and Figma to deliver creative solutions to commercial clients. Currently pursuing an audio visual arts degree from Kyiv International University while further honing design skills. Recently participated in a refugee monitoring initiative with ACTED international NGO, delegated by the UNHCR. Strongly committed to making a positive impact through design

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Visual Designer: full time

Ukraine

Sept 2019 - Apr 2020

"GVS" Typography Center:

• created book cover art graphics

#### Graphic Designer: part time

Ukraine

May 2020 - Aug 2020

Online Retail Network "Mobiloz":

 edited customer product photos for online listings

#### Content Maker: freelance

Ukraine

Aug 2021 - Currently

Employment per project

- filmed events: weddings, parties, tv-series production
- created content for instagram page

### Social Marketing: project

Ukraine

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Kyiv International University

- produced advertisement concepts
- draw animations and edited videos

# Enumerator: full time

Poland

May 2022 - Oct 2022

#### UNHCR ACTED

- interviewed refugees
- collected and reported data on refugees dislocation

### SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Lightroom, Premiere Pro) and DaVinci Resolve for video and photo editing and graphic design.
- Developing proficiency in creating interactive UI design prototypes in Figma
- Familiar with other design tools such as Illustrator and After Effects
- Skilled in curating and managing Instagram and TikTok pages, creating engaging content, and growing audience

### **EDUCATION**

### LANGUAGES

#### Kyiv International University

Sept 2020 - currently

Audiovisual Arts and Production.

Master of Arts Program

English, Ukranian, Russian